A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 5, Accession 2017:061 FA1472
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professorship Files, 1969-2001; 2
  - Tufts University, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1975-1994 (Box 77, Folder 520-521, Box 78, Folder 522-527)
  - Tulane University, 1979-1985 (Box 79, Folder 528-529)
  - Tulane University (Renewal), 1985-1990 (Box 79, Folder 530)
  - University of Chicago, 1974-2001 (Box 79, Folder 531-534, Box 80, Folder 535)
  - University of Southern California, 1991-2000 (Box 80, Folder 536-539)
  - Vanderbilt University, 1975-1987 (Box 81, Folder 540-543)
  - Washington University, 1980-1998 (Box 81, Folder 544-545)
  - Washington University - Report, 1989-1994 (Box 82, Folder 546)
  - Washington University (Renewal), 1986-1988 (Box 82, Folder 547)
  - Wellesley College, 1975-1989 (Box 82, Folder 548-550)
  - Wesleyan University, 1978-1993 (Box 82, Folder 551-552)
  - Wesleyan University - Report, 1989-1997 (Box 82, Folder 553)
  - Wheaton College, 1986-1990 (Box 83, Folder 554-558)
  - Wheaton College - Proposal (Renewal), 1990-1991 (Box 83, Folder 559)